

Jakarta, Indonesia 🏠

+62 852 6483 8044 🕓

Muhammadreza161@gmail.com ⊠

Github.com/muhammadreza161 💭

Muhammadreza161.github.io

Experience in the field of Web Development since 2021, starting as a Frontend Web Developer using various frameworks such as PHP Framework, JavaScript Framework, and CSS Framework and also using databases. Dedicated to being a Frontend Development.

# **Work Experience**

JANUARY 2023 - PRESENT

## Web Developer - IT Support | PT Brothersindo Saudara Sejati

- Website maintenance
- Provide technical support to users
- Manage the network, backup data and update software according to users needs

#### SEPTEMBER 2022 - NOVEMBER 2022

## Software Developer | PT Anabatic Technologies Tbk (PT IKI Karunia)

- Determine the structure and design of website pages
- Create face to face features that improve the user experience
- Ensure web design is able to maximize user experience

#### NOVEMBER 2021 - SEPTEMBER 2022

## Frontend Web Developer | PT Wells Management Smart

- Work closely with the backend team to develop the project
- Create face to face features that improve the user experience
- Ensure web design is able to maximize user experience

#### SEPTEMBER 2018 - SEPTEMBER 2019

#### Data Entry | Department Employment - Intern

- Collect and ensure completeness of all information before entering data into company software programs
- Enter personal customer information into a database that is collected on a form or spreadsheet
- Review all data to be reported to management

## Skills

- Html
- Css
- JavaScript
- Node Js
- React Js
- Vue JsLaravel (PHP)
- Bootsrap
- Version Control System (GIT)
- Rest API
- Wordpress
- MySQL
- Postman

- Corel Draw
- Figma
- Balsamiq Mockup
- Wireframing Prototype
- Microsoft Office

# **Education**

2016 - 2021

UNIVERSITAS PUTRA INDONESIA YPTK PADANG | INFORMATION SYSTEM (3.22)

2013 - 2016

SMAN NEGERI 2 KOTA PARIAMAN | IPS